A Guide to the Eleanor P. Sheppard Papers 1924-1978
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
- Series IV-Oversize, n.d. 1954-1975
  - Business and Professional WOmen's Club of Virginia 1968-1980, oversize (Box 31)
  - Campaign Eleanor Sheppard 1966-1979, oversize (Box 31)
  - Campaign 1971, oversize (Box 31)
  - Campaign 1975, oversize (Box 31)
  - Capital Square 1972-1976, oversize (Box 31)
  - Career Education Advisory Committee 1975-1977, oversize (Box 31)
  - Central Virginia Educational, T.V. 1964-1981, oversize (Box 31)
  - Central Virginia Educational Television 1984, oversize (Box 31)
  - Christmas Mother: Community Christmas Pageant 1974, oversize (Box 31)
  - City Council Campaigns 1962-1963, oversize (Box 31)
  - Civic Center 1956-1965, oversize (Box 31)
  - Collective Bargaining: Colleges 1977-1978, oversize (Box 31)
  - Collective Bargaining: Public Employees 1974-1977, oversize (Box 31)
  - Commission on the Status of Women 1968-1980, oversize (Box 31)
  - Commonwealth Girl Scout Council of Virginia 1968-1971, oversize (Box 31)
  - Commonwealth Girl Scout Council 1980, oversize (Box 31)
  - Community Advisory Board/Community Correctional Center Steering Committee 1973-1977, oversize (Box 31)
  - Community Improvement Program 1968-1970, oversize (Box 31)
  - Compensation/USRS and Travel Vouchers 1974-1978, oversize (Box 31)
  - Compulsory Education 1973-1977, oversize (Box 31)
  - Conference Roanoke, VA 1975, oversize (Box 31)
  - Conflict of Interest 1963-1976, oversize (Box 31)
  - Congratulations 1974-1976, oversize (Box 31)
  - Congratulatory Letters 1973 (Box 32)
  - Constitutional Officers 1971-1973 (Box 32)
  - Constitution: Commission to Revise 1968 (Box 32)
  - Constitution: Presentation to Electorate 1970 (Box 32)
  - Constitutional Revision 1969 (Box 32)
  - Correspondence 1972-1974 (Box 32)
  - Correspondence 1977 (Box 32)
  - Correspondence 1954-1975 (Box 32)
  - Correspondence/Non Personal 1963-1975 (Box 32)
  - Council Business 1958-1965 (Box 32)
  - Council Procedure 1967-1970 (Box 32)
  - Defense Advisory Committee on Women in the Services 1964 (Box 32)
  - Democratic Party and Caucus 1975-1977 (Box 32)
  - Election Campaign 1973 (Box 32)
  - Election Information 1975-1977 (Box 32)
  - Equal Rights 1973-1977 (Box 32)
  - Equal Rights Monitor Magazine 1976-1977 (Box 32)
  - General Assembly 1973-1977 (Box 32)
  - Girls State Auxiliary 1965 (Box 33)
  - Girls State Auxiliary 1968-1972 (Box 33)
  - Girls State Auxiliary 1973-1976 (Box 33)
  - Governors Commission 1963-1967 (Box 33)
  - Governor John N. Dalton 1975 (Box 33)
  - Governor Linwood Holton 1970-1974 (Box 33)
  - Governor Mills E. Godwin 1968-1977 (Box 33)
  - Greater Ginter Park Citizens Association 1959 (Box 33)
  - Historic Richmond Foundation 1957-1976 (Box 33)
  - House Bills 1969 (Box 33)
  - House Bills 1969 (Box 33)
  - House Bills 1973-1977 (Box 33)
  - House of Delegates 1973 (Box 33)
  - House of Delegates 1974 (Box 33)
  - Housing Opportunities Made Equal (H.O.M.E.) 1980-1983 (Box 33)
  - Institute for Business and Community Development 1966-1971 (Box 33)
  - International Toastmistress Clubs Commonwealth Chapter 1965-1970 (Box 33)
  - Invitations 1954-1966 (Box 33)
  - Invitations 1954-1966 (Box 33)
  - Invitations 1967-1970 (Box 33)
  - Invitations 1967-1970 (Box 33)
  - Invitations 1967-1970 (Box 33)
  - Invitations 1967-1970 (Box 33)
  - Jaycees 1964 (Box 34)
  - Jimmy Carter 1976 (Box 34)
  - John Marshall Youth Camp 1966-1967 (Box 34)
  - Joint Subcommittee on the Placement of Children for Adoption 1976 (Box 34)
  - J. Sergeant Reynolds Nursing Program Advisory Board 1975-1982 (Box 34)
  - Junior League Community 1973-1977 (Box 34)
  - Letters to Constituents from Eleanor P. Sheppard 1973-1977 (Box 34)
  - Local Subsidy 1952-1953 (Box 34)
  - Lotteries and Parimutual Betting #1 of 2 1968-1974 (Box 34)
  - Lotteries and Parimutual Betting #2 of 2 1971-1974 (Box 34)
  - Maymont/Articles of incorporation (Box 34)
  - Maymont 1959-1962 (Box 34)
  - Maymont 1962-1967 (Box 34)
  - Maymont 1968-1970 (Box 34)
  - Maymont 1970-1975 (Box 34)
  - Maymont 1975-1976 (Box 34)
  - Maymont 1976-1978 (Box 34)
  - Maymont 1978-1980 (Box 34)
  - Medical College of Virginia 1976 (Box 34)
  - Mental Retardation Subcommittee-Services Board 1970-1976 (Box 34)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 34)
  - National Laboratory for Higher Education 1972-1974 (Box 35)
  - National Order of Women Legislators 1976-1979 (Box 35)
  - National Uniform Traffic Laws and Ordinances Committee 1975-1978 (Box 35)
  - Newspaper Articles 1-20 N.D. (Box 35)
  - Newsletter-University of Virginia 1974 (Box 35)
  - Northside Community Council 1966-1970 (Box 35)
  - North Richmond Branch Metro Richmond YMCA (Box 35)
  - Pages Session 1976 (Box 35)
  - Page Applications Session 1977 (Box 35)
  - Photos, n.d. (Box 35)
  - Programs, n.d. (Box 35)
  - Programs, n.d. (Box 35)
  - Programs, n.d. (Box 35)
  - Programs, n.d. (Box 35)
  - Programs, n.d. (Box 35)
  - Programs 1964 (Box 36)
  - Publications 1962 (Box 36)
  - Publications, n.d. (Box 36)
  - Publications, n.d. (Box 36)
  - Publications 1968-1978 (Box 36)
  - Publications 1962-1973 (Box 36)
  - Regrets 1973-1976 (Box 36)
  - Report To The Governor On Consumer Education 1976-1977 (Box 36)
  - Resumes: Legislative Assistant for Eleanor Sheppard 1973 (Box 36)
  - Resumes: Legislative Assistant for Eleanor Sheppard 1974 (Box 36)
  - Resumes: Legislative Assistant for Eleanor Sheppard 1975 (Box 36)
  - Resumes: Legislative Assistant for Eleanor Sheppard 1976 (Box 36)
  - Richmond Area Community Council 1970-1975 (Box 36)
  - Richmond Area Democratic Women's Club 1977-1978 (Box 36)
  - Richmond Area Heart Association 1968-1972 (Box 36)
  - Richmond Area Psychiatric Clinic Advisory Board 1968-1975 (Box 36)
  - Richmond City Judges 1972-1977 (Box 36)
  - Richmond City Library 1958-1964 (Box 36)
  - Richmond Civil War Centennial 1960-1965 (Box 36)
  - Richmond Council of Garden Clubs 1973-1982 (Box 36)
  - Richmond Experiment In International Living 1968-1978 (Box 36)
  - Richmond Independence Bicentennial Commission 1976-1980 (Box 36)
  - Richmond International Council 1966-1972 (Box 36)
  - Richmond Metro YMCA Board of Directors 1977-1980 (Box 36)
  - Richmond Metro YMCA Policies 1976-1985 (Box 36)
  - Richmond Symphony 1966-1980 (Box 36)
  - Science Museum of Virginia 1968-1974 (Box 36)
  - Sears Roebuck Board of Directors 1971-1972 (Box 36)
  - Strategic Air Command Info Kit 1975 (Box 36)
  - Teachers Salaries 1954 (Box 36)
  - Thank You Letters 1975 (Box 36)
  - Travel Memorabilia, n.d. (Box 36)
  - Twenty Three Hundred Club 1964-1966 (Box 36)
  - Urban Policy Conference Program May 27, 1964 (Box 37)
  - Urban Policy Conference Program June 24, 1964 (Box 37)
  - Urban Policy Conference Program January 13, 1965 (Box 37)
  - Urban Policy Conference Program Feb. 3, 1965
  - Urban Policy Conference Program May 19, 1965 (Box 37)
  - Urban Policy Conference Program Feb. 24, 1965 (Box 37)
  - Urban Policy Conference Program May 17, 1965 (Box 37)
  - Urban Policy Conference Program April 7, 1965 (Box 37)
  - Urban Policy Conference Program June 8, 1965 (Box 37)
  - Virginia Association of Workers for the Blind inc. 1967-1973 (Box 37)
  - Virginia Council On Social Welfare-Rep. RACC 1973-1975 (Box 37)
  - Virginia Historic Landmarks Committee: Notes On Virginia 1973-1976 (Box 37)
  - Virginia Metropolitan Areas Study Commission 1967-1969 (Box 37)
  - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts 1964-1976 (Box 37)
  - Virginia Museum O Fine Arts 1985-1988 (Box 37)
  - Virginia Plan for Higher Education 1989 (Box 37)
  - Virginia State Library 1958-1977 (Box 37)
  - Voting Precincts 1970-1971 (Box 37)
  - Voting Records 1972-1977 (Box 37)
  - YMCA Board and Study 1968-1969 (Box 37)
  - YMCA Board and Study 1969-1973 (Box 37)
  - YMCA Human Resources 1975-1981 (Box 37)
  - Ephemeral (Box 38)
  - Index Cards containing names and addresses (Box 39)